export default [
  {
    question: "5 + 2 - 3 = ....",
    choices: ["4", "5", "3", "2"],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "8 - 4 + 1 = ....",
    choices: ["4", "5", "6", "3"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "6 + 3 - 5 = ....",
    choices: ["5", "3", "4", "6"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "7 - 2 + 2 = ....",
    choices: ["6", "7", "5", "8"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "9 - 3 - 2 = ....",
    choices: ["4", "3", "5", "6"],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "2 + 4 - 1 = ....",
    choices: ["6", "4", "5", "3"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "3 + 5 - 4 = ....",
    choices: ["4", "3", "5", "6"],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "10 - 2 + 1 = ....",
    choices: ["7", "8", "9", "6"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "4 + 1 - 3 = ....",
    choices: ["1", "3", "2", "4"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "7 - 5 + 3 = ....",
    choices: ["5", "4", "3", "2"],
    answer: 0,
  },
];
